<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>28.07.2018</title>
    <link>http://geneandmelina.com/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on 28.07.2018</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Gene &amp; Melina</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 12:36:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://geneandmelina.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Our story</title>
      <link>http://geneandmelina.com/our_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 12:36:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geneandmelina.com/our_story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Melina and Gene never really met someone who understood their eclectic hobbies: their love for the outdoors, their need to climb things, why melodic death metal is the best metal, or that life is much better with a pet (or ten).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day, unbeknownst to each other, Gene and Melina went to hang out with their friend Sam, and little did they know they would meet a person who incidentally had the same interests and passions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few words were exchanged that first night between them, but perhaps a smile or a passing comment caught Gene&amp;rsquo;s eye, and for the next month, he persisted to get a date with Melina. When she finally accepted, their fates became intertwined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their relationship grew quickly: moving in together slightly a year later, adopting each other&amp;rsquo;s pets shortly afterwards, and now officially joining their families together on July 28, 2018, 5 years and 1 day since they first started dating.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event details</title>
      <link>http://geneandmelina.com/event_details/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 12:36:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geneandmelina.com/event_details/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://santacruzmah.org/&#34;&gt;Santa Cruz Museum of Art and History&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d3187.473852830684!2d-122.02768018512022!3d36.97462096556226!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x808e402672dbb76b%3A0x88dee35639218ba8!2sMuseum+of+Art+%26+History!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1500222553488&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;450&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;border:0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Date and time&lt;/b&gt;: 28.07.2018&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Details&lt;/b&gt;: coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts</title>
      <link>http://geneandmelina.com/gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 12:36:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://geneandmelina.com/gifts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What we want most of our wedding is to have our closest friends and family in the same room to celebrate this special day with us. We consider your presence to be a present. That said, if you would really like to get us something tangible, please donate to some of the charities that we support ourselves:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.againstmalaria.com/&#34;&gt;Against Malaria Foundation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
Malaria kills half a million people every year and 400 million fall ill. Every death from malaria is preventable. The Against Malaria Foundation helps protect people from malaria by funding anti-malaria nets and working with distribution partners to ensure they are used; it&amp;rsquo;s the greatest impact per dollar.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.againstmalaria.com/Donation.aspx&#34;&gt;Donate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.karimufoundation.org/&#34;&gt;Karimu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
Karimu believes that Tanzanian villagers understand their own needs far better than any outsiders and can address them if given a little help. The partnership between Karimu and the villagers has empowered the community to improve education, healthcare, agriculture, and access to clean water. In the past two years, Melina&amp;rsquo;s parents have sponsored projects like a new maternity clinic and school and traveled to the Babati district to work alongside the villagers to build these facilities. They have committed to new projects for 2018, 2019, and beyond.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.karimufoundation.org/&#34;&gt;Donate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://bamru.org&#34;&gt;BAMRU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
Melina is a volunteer with the Bay Area Mountain Rescue Unit (BAMRU), a volunteer wilderness search and rescue team specialized in helping lost or stranded people in difficult terrain, challenging weather, or high altitude. All of their funding for searches, training, supplies, and equipment come from donations and member contributions with some assistance from the San Mateo County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Emergency Services Bureau.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://bamru.org/donate.html&#34;&gt;Donate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>